

ERIK UGARTE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER



+46 737728175



erik-nu@hotmail.com



in https://www.linkedin.com/in/erik-ugarte-786267159/

PROJECTS

- SolidSport 2021 Developing the main platform
- Dewire at Knightec 2022 Cloudhub - System developer
- Dewire at Knightec 2022-2023 **Boule - Frontend developer**

EXPERTIES

- Public Speaking
- Teamwork
- Team Leadership
- Social
- Adaptable
- Innovative

LANGUAGES

Swedish

English

Spanish

French

ABOUT ME

I am an experienced front-end developer working mostly with React. I have a few years of experience of working and I am currently hired at Dewire-Knightec as a consultant. Other than working as a developer I spend a lot of my time coaching basketball. As of this moment I am coaching the men's team for Central Basket in Stockholm and I am also part of the coaching staff for the Swedish men's U16 national team.

EDUCATION

2016-2019

KTH - ROYAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY Computer orientation, communcation and IT

• 2019-2021

STI - STOCKHOLM INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY Mobile app developer

CAREER SUMMARY

- 2021 **SOLIDSPORT Developer intern**
- 2021-2022 **SOLIDSPORT** Develeoper
- 2022-2023 **DEWIRE AT KNIGHTEC** Front-end developer

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

















